this one comes in from Niha D from money
Control
Pro today's talk idea is icsa Lombard
General Insurance company after merging
the business of bti EXA General
insurance with itself in F22 uh the
insurer has been uh focusing on the
organic growth IC Lombard has
strengthened its Market position as the
premium growth for the company remains
about the industry growth while the
motor insurance segment has seen a
subdued growth health insurance segment
has emerged as a key growth driver for
the company uh to to capture the
opportunity in the retail Health segment
uh ICA Lombard has been increasing its
distribution Network by adding uh retail
health agency managers uh it anticipates
uh the growth in health business to
accelerate in the coming quarters as the
Salesforce gets productive uh the
insurer reported uh a combined ratio of
around 104% in the first 9 months of the
current fiscal uh which is underwriting
loss however it was offset by higher
investment income leading to overall
profits management is confident of
achieving height in growth in premium
and improving the combined ratio to 102%
by fi25 which is a very encouraging
guidance on both growth as well as
profitability the stock has rallied
around 177% in the past 1 month and in
terms of valuation it is currently
trading at a very rich valuation of
around uh AG times uh Book value as of
December end however the premium
valuation is justified by the superior
franchise and sector uh Tailwinds
long-term investors can add the stock on
Deb
okay all right thanks a lot for that ni
for the time being though we'll slip
into a short break on the other side B
get chatting with the management of
Rashi peripherals don't go
anywhere